hotrodders.com 2010-12-31

# Hotrodders.com Privacy Policy

Hotrodders.com takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. 

**What this Privacy Policy Covers**

  * This Privacy Policy covers Hotrodders.com's treatment of personally identifiable information that Hotrodders.com collects when you are on the Hotrodders.com website, and when you use Hotrodders.com's services. This policy also covers Hotrodders.com's treatment of any personally identifiable information that Hotrodders.com's business partners share with Hotrodders.com. 
  * This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Hotrodders.com does not own or control, or to people that Hotrodders.com does not employ or manage. 

**Information Collection and Use**

  * Hotrodders.com collects personally identifiable information when you register for a Hotrodders.com account. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

  * Hotrodders.com will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone. Hotrodders.com will only send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when:  

    * We have your consent to share the information; 
    * We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; or 
    * We find that your actions on our website violate the Hotrodders.com [Terms of Service](http://www.hotrodders.com/terms.html). 

**Cookies**

  * Hotrodders.com may set and access Hotrodders.com cookies on your computer. In addition, because of the use of Google Adsense on this website, third parties may be placing and reading cookies on your browser, or using web beacons to collect information in the course of ads being served. 
  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

**Security**

  * Your Hotrodders Account Information is password-protected for your privacy and security.
